https://www.keithcompany.com/privacy_policy.html

Adv. Materials Furnaces & Kilns
Calcining Kilns (Ceramics + Advanced Materials)
Metallic Heating Elements
MoSiO2 Elements (MolyD or Molybdenum Disilicide)
Privacy Policy
By accessing or using the KeithCompany.com website, you agree to the terms of the Keith Company, Inc. (hereafter referred to as Keith) Online Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. Keith reserves the right to change the Online Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current version of the Online Privacy Policy at the time of such use.Collection of personal informationWhen you engage in certain activities on this site, Keith may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, Keith may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), e-mail address, employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal identifying information. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide may be identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.When you submit company information to Keith on this site, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which Keith and its affiliates or subsidiaries maintain offices, including without limitation, the United States.How your personal information is usedKeith collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. The information that you provide is also used as part of our effort to keep you informed about product upgrades, special offers, and other products and services of Keith.It is against Keith's policy to provide any of your information to any organization that is not an affiliate or subsidiary of Keith.Use of cookiesWhen you visit KeithCompany.com, you can surf the site anonymously and access important information without revealing your identity. In order to improve our site, we may use "cookies" to track your visit. A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a Web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card, recording your passwords and preferences. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. Some Web pages may require an authorization. In this case, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies may not be able to access those pages.While Keith may use cookies to track your visit to KeithCompany.com, and our Web servers automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer, this information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided Keith with personal information.Updating your personal informationYou have the right to access and correct your personal information at any time. You may access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences by writing or calling Keith at the address mentioned on our website:Please include your name, address, and/or e-mail address when you contact us.Privacy related complaintsIf you believe that Keith has not complied with this Online Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information, you may write the Keith Webmaster under Contact Us on the website.In your letter, please describe in as much detail as possible the ways in which you believe that the Keith Online Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly.Also, please note that Keith is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-Keith Web sites to which KeithCompany.com or any other Keith Web site
Home
About Us
Keith Company - History in Pictures
Mergers and Acquisitions by Keith Company
Recco Furnaces & Heating Elements
KMI Refractories
CFF Kilns & Furnaces
Employment at Keith Company
Calcining Kilns (Ceramics + Advanced Materials)
MoSiO2 Elements (MolyD or Molybdenum Disilicide)
Phone: (562) 948-3636 | Fax: (562) 949-3696 | Email: info@keithcompany.com
